dcdmedia.net 2017-12-15

# Privacy - DCDMedia

Pursuant to this Agreement, DCDMedia Inc and Publisher shall agree to the following terms and conditions for the receipt of advertising materials ("Creative") from advertising Customers ("Customers"). This includes the serving, tracking and reporting of each Campaign made available on the DCDMedia Affiliate Network (the "Network") to Publisher and Publisher Websites ("Websites").

**USE POLICY:**

**Data Integrity**  
DCDMedia takes your privacy seriously. All sensitive information is encrypted with SSL and our server is routinely audited to ensure a secure environment for DCDMedia users. 

**Cookies**  
DCDMedia uses cookies to identify the individual with his or her corresponding tracking data that resides in DCDMedia's database. Individuals who use the Website need to accept cookies in order to use all of the features and functionality of the Website. 

**Web Beacons**  
A web beacon is a small pixel image that is placed on a website or in an email which is used to monitor behavior of a user visiting a website or email and store their information. This allows DCDMedia to track certain web sites an individual visits online. Web beacons are used to determine products or services an individual may be interested in, and to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes. 

**Tracking Data**  
To ensure fraud-free service, DCDMedia's lead tracking system gathers IP addresses and other user variables along with setting tracking cookies. This information is used to prevent users from abusing advertiser terms and conditions with methods such as multiple completions per person and fraudulent completions. 

**Outside Information**  
DCDMedia may receive information about individuals from Third Parties or from other sources of information outside of DCDMedia including information located in public databases (Outside Information). 

**Individual Information**  
As used herein, Individual Information means Survey Information, Third Party List Information, Other Information, Technology Information, and Outside Information, and any other information DCDMedia gathers or receives about individuals such as usage data, file transfer and viewing data. 

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act**  
DCDMedia will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If DCDMedia obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because it does not collect such information, DCDMedia has no such information to use or to disclose to Third Parties. DCDMedia has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). 

**California Residents**  
As per California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California residents may request information about the disclosure of their personal details to third parties by contacting us. 

**Deleting & Updating Your Information**  
If you would like to delete or update the personally identifiable information that we have collected from you (name, address, etc.), simply send your request to [Support@AdWorkMedia.com](mailto:Su%70port@%41%64W%6Frk%4De%64i%61.c%6Fm). We will process your request, where possible and subject to the terms and conditions contained herein, within a reasonable period of time after receipt. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**Legal Process**  
DCDMedia may disclose Individual Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, and other legal processes. 

**Advertiser Cookies and Web Beacons**  
DCDMedia does not control Advertisers' use of tracking mechanisms and DCDMedia has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about individuals. 

**Links**  
The Website and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the web sites of Third Parties. DCDMedia is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites. Linked web sites may contain links to web sites maintained by Third Parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. DCDMedia does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such Third Party web sites. The inclusion of a link to a web site does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization. 

**International**  
Anyone using the Website outside of the United States acknowledges that personal information will be collected and stored by DCDMedia in the United States. By using the Website, you consent to the transfer of information to and/or storage of information outside of your country and in the United States. 

**Information collected from Third Parties**  
DCDMedia collects information from individuals when an individual provides information to a Third Party and DCDMedia subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise acquires the information from the Third Party (the Seller). Such purchased information may include, but is not limited to, an individual's name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), SMS messaging details (e.g. date, time and content of the SMS message), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the individual may have provided to the Seller (together, Third Party List Information). When acquiring Third Party List Information, DCDMedia seeks assurances from the Seller that the Seller has a right to transfer the Third Party List Information to DCDMedia and that the Seller has a right to provide offers from advertisers to the individuals whose personal information is included on the Seller's list. 

**Contact**  
If you have any questions or comments related to this privacy policy please [**contact us**](http://dcdmedia.net/home/contact).
